{
  "results": [
    {
      "question": "Match the term 'cost rate table' to its description:",
      "correct_answer": "h. resource pay rates that are stored on the Costs tab of the Resource Information dialog box",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. an absolute quantity of material resources will be used, no matter the duration of the task",
        "b. the total work of a resource\u2019s task assignments is exactly equal to that resource\u2019s work capacity",
        "c. a resource is assigned to do more work than can be done within the normal capacity of the resource"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Match the term 'underallocated' to its description:",
      "correct_answer": "e. the work assigned to a resource is less than the resource\u2019s maximum capacity",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. an absolute quantity of material resources will be used, no matter the duration of the task",
        "b. the total work of a resource\u2019s task assignments is exactly equal to that resource\u2019s work capacity",
        "c. a resource is assigned to do more work than can be done within the normal capacity of the resource"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Match the term 'variable consumption rate' to its description:",
      "correct_answer": "d. the amount of the material resource consumed is dependent upon the duration of the task",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. an absolute quantity of material resources will be used, no matter the duration of the task",
        "b. the total work of a resource\u2019s task assignments is exactly equal to that resource\u2019s work capacity",
        "c. a resource is assigned to do more work than can be done within the normal capacity of the resource"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Match the term 'units' to its description:",
      "correct_answer": "i. the portion of a resource\u2019s capacity devoted to work on a specific task",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. an absolute quantity of material resources will be used, no matter the duration of the task",
        "b. the total work of a resource\u2019s task assignments is exactly equal to that resource\u2019s work capacity",
        "c. a resource is assigned to do more work than can be done within the normal capacity of the resource"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Match the term 'allocation' to its description:",
      "correct_answer": "f. the process of delaying or splitting a resource\u2019s work on a task to resolve an overallocation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. an absolute quantity of material resources will be used, no matter the duration of the task",
        "b. the total work of a resource\u2019s task assignments is exactly equal to that resource\u2019s work capacity",
        "c. a resource is assigned to do more work than can be done within the normal capacity of the resource"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Match the term 'fixed consumption rate' to its description:",
      "correct_answer": "a. an absolute quantity of material resources will be used, no matter the duration of the task",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "d. the amount of the material resource consumed is dependent upon the duration of the task",
        "b. the total work of a resource\u2019s task assignments is exactly equal to that resource\u2019s work capacity",
        "c. a resource is assigned to do more work than can be done within the normal capacity of the resource"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Match the term 'overallocated' to its description:",
      "correct_answer": "g. the maximum capacity of a resource to accomplish work",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. an absolute quantity of material resources will be used, no matter the duration of the task",
        "b. the total work of a resource\u2019s task assignments is exactly equal to that resource\u2019s work capacity",
        "c. a resource is assigned to do more work than can be done within the normal capacity of the resource"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Match the term 'resource leveling' to its description:",
      "correct_answer": "c. a resource is assigned to do more work than can be done within the normal capacity of the resource",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. an absolute quantity of material resources will be used, no matter the duration of the task",
        "b. the total work of a resource\u2019s task assignments is exactly equal to that resource\u2019s work capacity",
        "f. the process of delaying or splitting a resource\u2019s work on a task to resolve an overallocation"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Match the term 'fully allocated' to its description:",
      "correct_answer": "b. the total work of a resource\u2019s task assignments is exactly equal to that resource\u2019s work capacity",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. an absolute quantity of material resources will be used, no matter the duration of the task",
        "c. a resource is assigned to do more work than can be done within the normal capacity of the resource",
        "f. the process of delaying or splitting a resource\u2019s work on a task to resolve an overallocation"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Match the term 'Max. Units' to its description:",
      "correct_answer": "j. the measurement of a resource\u2019s capacity to work",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "a. an absolute quantity of material resources will be used, no matter the duration of the task",
        "c. a resource is assigned to do more work than can be done within the normal capacity of the resource",
        "f. the process of delaying or splitting a resource\u2019s work on a task to resolve an overallocation"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Resource leveling cannot always resolve all resource overallocations. (T/F)",
      "correct_answer": "T",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "F"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "A resource cannot have both a cost per use and a cost derived from its pay rate. (T/F)",
      "correct_answer": "T",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "F"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Resource leveling never changes who is assigned to tasks or the total work value of those assignments. (T/F)",
      "correct_answer": "F",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "T"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "You can manually resolve a resource overallocation by replacing the overallocated resource with another resource. (T/F)",
      "correct_answer": "T",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "F"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "You can assign two types of material consumption rates in Microsoft Project. (T/F)",
      "correct_answer": "F",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "T"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The settings in the Resource Leveling dialog box apply to all of the project schedules you work with in Microsoft Project. (T/F)",
      "correct_answer": "T",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "F"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "You can have up to six cost rate tables for a resource. (T/F)",
      "correct_answer": "T",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "F"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "It is not acceptable to allow a minor overallocation to remain in a schedule. (T/F)",
      "correct_answer": "F",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "T"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The default rate table in Microsoft Project is Rate Table 1. (T/F)",
      "correct_answer": "T",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "F"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "When a variable consumption rate is assigned to a material resource, and the duration of the task to which it is assigned changes, so do the calculated amount and cost of the material resource. (T/F)",
      "correct_answer": "T",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "F"
      ]
    }
  ],
  "setCount": 1
}